Original Story by G.E.M.
All Songs Written by G.E.M.
Chapter 1: Gloria
Fallen leaves and greyish sky
New season will soon arrive
A humble butterfly amid a whole wide world
Will she be able to wait for someone’s comfort
Before the dawn, we’re all blind
My tears are scattered through the wilderness
Next to my ears, I recurrently hear
The looming and healing whispers:
Gloria, don't be afraid
Gloria, there’s no fear in love
My love will stream endlessly like a river
My love will cleanse all wounds
You do not need to be strong to stand beside me
Let me bear weight and your heavy burden
If you are lost, I will wander by your side
If you are tired, I will take you to fly
Gloria, don't be afraid
Gloria, there’s no fear in love
My love has the depth of the sea
My love can endure all catastrophes
Gloria, don't be afraid
Gloria, there’s no fear in love
My love will transcend time
My love has stayed and will never depart
Gloria, don't be afraid
Gloria, there’s no fear in love
I am love, I am always patient
I am waiting, waiting for your comeback
Chapter 2: Hell
Is it my cruel hallucination
Or are you truly a delusion
You let me have a glimpse of heaven
But then you let my soul leaving
Your love is so surreal
Leaving horrifying memories that I dare to be real
You take me to hell
From Heaven I fell
You lit up the fire of jealousy
It ignites and it rises
You cannot deny
You spark one’s devil impulse
How many shapes you can fake
How much ache a word can make
How many “me” are around you
How dangerous if suspicion rises
Am I prone to injury
Or the truth must lead to misery
You take me to hell
From Heaven I fell
You lit up the fire of jealousy
It ignites and it rises
You cannot deny
You spark one’s devil impulse
I am imprisoned without my pulse
You take me to hell
From Heaven I fell
You put on a fire of jealousy
You made me believe
You loved me indeed
The truth is you don't know what love is
You lit up the fire of jealousy
You incite the devil’s game
You take me to hell
You lit up the fire of jealousy
From Heaven I fell
You spark one’s devil impulse
I am imprisoned without my pulse
Chapter 3: Me & You
Wish to set off with you to a far away place
Where our hearts are tied in our private space
Without the need to care the stare of other faces
Wishing the true existence of such place
Where our hearts are tied in our private space
Wrapping us in the cave till the end of all age
Let them fail
in seeking you
in seeking me in a hide and seek game
Just me and you
As the world has been disappointing
But I've got you
I only need you to feel enlightening
Just me and you
I only care about me and you
Tell me you feel it too
Baby just me and you
Just me and you
As the Moon will only orbit the Earth all day
As lovers shall hold each other in the darkest days
As I wish to escape from the world and occupy your days
As if I’m living in your gaze
Let them fail
in seeking you
in seeking me in a hide and seek game
Just me and you
As the world has been disappointing
But I've got you
I only need you to feel enlightening
Just me and you
I only care about me and you
Tell me you feel it too
Baby just me and you
Just me and you
Are you free tomorrow?
Yes, I'm free every day
I want to see you
Chapter 4: Man Who Laughs
You are not the first one to depart
You are not the last scar in my heart
When the night arrives, no one can hold on to daylight
Don’t worry about me, and let me fly like a lost kite
I'll keep smiling and laughing
I'll always put on my laughing face
I long so much for your happiness
Even if it means my loneliness
Why are there tears in my smile
And why couldn't you notice
I cry and I smile
But I am without a choice
I am not the first wounded soul
And will not be the most broken soul
I come alone and shall leave alone
Don’t worry about me, just smile as we part
So I'll keep smiling and laughing
I'll always put on my laughing face
I long so much for your happiness
Even if it means my loneliness
Why are there tears in my smile
And why couldn't you notice
I cry and I smile
But both are sincere
So I'll keep smiling and laughing
I'll always put on my laughing face
I long so much for your happiness
Even if it means my loneliness
With smile, I will bring you the tears on the verge of my eyes
Which will turn into your guarding star
Save the heavens for you
Save the darkness for myself
Chapter 5: Solitude
Don’t wanna go home
Songs are still playing
No urge for leaving
Don’t wanna go home
The dawn has not arrived
So as the sober time
Lonely night
can you just stay for me
For my sake, for one more night
One more night
Be by my side
Can you accompany me
Accompany me for one more night
One more night
I have a bad habit
Having a bee in my bonnet at night
It’s easy to feel sad when laying on bed
When the light’s out, emotions burst out
Truth be told I have strived to appeal
but all my efforts seem to fall ill
If it’s me who’s overburdened by troubles
Can I be granted a cuddle
A feeling that I can’t utter
The feeling that I can’t utter
As if my heart has a missing piece
Yet it’s not as down as one would feel
I can’t let out my sorrow
I can’t let out my tears
At least don’t ruin the vibe
At least I’ve got you tonight
Cuz I
Don’t wanna go home
Songs are still playing
No urge for leaving
Don’t wanna go home
The dawn has not arrived
So as the sober time
Lonely night
Can you just stay for me
For my sake, for one more night
One more night
Be by my side
Can you accompany me
Accompany me for one more night
One more night
Not an addict of liquor
but I'm afraid to be sober
So I rather change the world’s character
to hold a distorted world a bit longer, and longer
I don’t want to stay awake till dawn
but I fear the silence in my room
So I rather let the vision overlapped
let it be blurred, and blurred
Tell me
(What would I face if I choose to love?)
Where should I hide
Stay with me
(Pray about it)
To shun from solitude temporarily
Cuz I don't wanna
Don’t wanna go home
Songs are still playing
No urge for leaving
Don’t wanna go home
The dawn has not arrived
So as the sober time
Lonely night
Don’t wanna go home
One more night
No urge for leaving
Oh just be by my side
Don’t wanna go home
Oh one more night
One more night
Lonely night
It's a lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely night
Stay with me one more night
Oh just be by my side
By my side
Oh one more night
One more night
Do you wish to delete [GLORIA] (no, yes)
Chapter 6: Passion
(Murderer)
Dear Father
Why my heart torn day and night
Why the world turns uglier day by day
Being crushed by this sickness every day
I am on the verge to burst
Their mouths are filled with filthy dirt
Throwing mud to others, when would you punish them
Am I asked to pretend blind
So as to suppress my inner flame
They proclaim to be just, and roar without constraints
Tread over others with their vicious words
There are daggers in their smile, poison in their words
Defeating so many of us
Look, their spit has turned to showers
Turning roads into steel wires
Facing these ruthless villain
One could only shut one’s ears to avoid deluge
In the nameless arena
Conversations have turned into a lake of fire
Haters march with their chests up high
Accusations have never died
Their joy is built on other’s grave
Unwilling to spare a life
Heresy is not the exclusive to Lucifer
It’s bestowed on terrorists on keyboard
Hiding behind their computers
Ferocious faces to my disgust (What the ****)
My merciful father, wouldn’t you have rage?
Or just treat them as careless mistakes and don’t engage
I want to follow your steps and walk on your path
Yet I don’t know how to forgive
How can I forgive
How can I…
All these devils, shoulder to shoulder
Lining up to take me drown
Though I go through the valley of deep shade
He shows me the way for His name's sake
I'm in a dark age
Please have mercy on me
Cuz Father
My heart aches
Can someone rescue me
Save me from drowning tides
Their mouths are filled with filthy dirt
Throwing mud to others, when would you punish them
Am I asked to pretend blind
So as to suppress my inner flame
Dear Father
Why my heart torn day and night
Why the world turns uglier day by day
Chapter 7: Ice Age
I am drowned in a teary sea
Needing thee but you are not here
Showing no care for me and my heavy dress
It’s duty that buries love
Making us forget how to love
Lovers gradually feel hard to love
Our love has reached the Ice Age
Covered with heavy snow and hit by a bleak white rage
When did our love turn cold from the heated stage
Our love is frozen by you
Will it has a next page
“I let go” in the face of others
“I let go” in the lie to my heart
To deceive my broken heart,
To make myself less pitiful
It’s pride that buries our love
and pretends the absence of scars
The lines beneath my heart
Can never be uttered
Our love has reached the Ice Age
Covered with heavy snow and hit by a bleak white rage
When did our love turn cold from the heated stage
Our love is frozen by you
Will it has a next page
Since when lovers start to hurt each other
Why would us build wall to fend off each other
(If God let you see)
From endless chat to speechless scat
We were one but now with no love for each other
Since when we start to hurt each other
Why would us build wall to fend off each other
From endless chat to speechless scat
We were fearless but now love to fear
Our love has reached the Ice Age
Covered with heavy snow and hit by a bleak white rage
( Please hand this letter to the first person who orders the Silver Storm )
When did our love turn cold from the heated stage
Our love is frozen by you
Will it has a next page
Chapter 8: Young Man & Sea
Was devoted to love
Why, oh why, am left with a broken soul
Was filled with expectation
Why, oh why, am left with scattered scars
That brutal sea
Hasn’t it defeated me subsequently
Why, oh why, I woke
How shall I exist in this reality
Was devoted to love
Why, oh why, am left with a broken soul
Was filled with expectation
Why, oh why, am left with scattered scars
That brutal sea
Hasn’t it defeated me subsequently
Why, oh why, I woke
How shall I exist in this reality
Chapter 9: Old Man & Sea
If the flower is doomed to wither
Will you supply it with daily water
If sunflowers refuse to turn their faces
Will you still stay for their change of mind
Time and again, the shore pushes away the waves
Yet, waves come back again and again
Love has not changed for eternity
Be it you stay or you leave
I still love without reservation
Though my soul may turn into remains
I am still filled with hope
Though my body may be full of scars
No matter how brutal the sea batters
I shall never surrender
For love, I exist
For love, I’m alive
If love is absent in one’s life it will be a pale life
Look, the shore pushes away the waves
Yet, waves come back again and again
Love has not changed for eternity
Be it you stay or you leave
I still love without reservation
Though my soul may turn into remains
I am still filled with hope
Though my body may be full of scars
No matter how brutal the sea batters
I shall never surrender
For love, I exist. For love, I’m alive
If love is absent in one’s life it will be a pale life
Even if you push me away again
I shall come back once and again
Love has not changed for eternity
For love, I exist. For love, I’m alive.
Chapter 10: Find You
Maybe you are not aware
How good you are in my stare
Unfamiliar to embrace to which you spare
So you struggle, so you want to disappear
But you may not be aware
I will follow the feather that fell from you
the mud you streaked
And run toward you at full speed
Cuz I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I find you
I will find you
No matter how rugged or smooth the path may be
I will never turn my back to you
I will pursue you, wherever you go
I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I can find you
From Heaven to Earth, no one can stop my pursuit
No matter you stand at apex or under abyss
I'll come and find you
I want you to know
You are the apple I want to hold in my palms
You are the most beautiful psalm
When I hear it, it’s the most gentle balm
Cuz I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I find you
I will find you
No matter how rugged or smooth the path may be
I will never turn my back to you
I will pursue you, wherever you go
I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I find you
From Heaven to Earth, no one can stop my pursuit
No matter you stand at apex or under abyss
I'll come and find you
No matter you advance, or you’re lost
You are glad, or you are sad
You once believed, or never be
You can see clearly, or in the mist
If you are far away, I guard
If you are fickle, I stand
If you don’t care, I care
Cuz I, cuz I
I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I find you
I will find you
No matter how rugged or smooth the path may be
I will never turn my back to you
I will pursue you, wherever you go
I'll come and find you
Oh anywhere til I can find you
From Heaven to Earth, no one can stop my pursuit
No matter you stand at apex or under abyss
I'll come and find you
Chapter 11: F = mw^2r
If I speak my mind with all my trust
My love is always regarded as dust
Across generations, waiting for you to wake up
But out of love, I will be patient for you to be willing
(If God let you see)
When you smile, you could grab me
(If perfection only exist in the virtual world, would you still love the real me?)
(I live across the street, 7th floor. Gloria.)
Yet when you run, you forget about me
I put choices in your hands
For your desire to leave, I stand
I let you have my bleeding heart
I let you choose to treasure or discard
Gutted, my sorrow stays in my heart
I always cherish your leaving heart
It may take forever for you to hand in your heart
But I keep on loving you and never depart
Before you fall, I foresaw
The dark and cold side in your heart
But I also hear, in the silent night
Your tears are all over your face, and you silently pray
When you call, I will come over
But you prefer your lonely slumber
I put choices in your hands
For your desire to leave, I stand
I let you have my bleeding heart
I let you choose to treasure or discard
Gutted, my sorrow stays in my heart
I always cherish your leaving heart
It may take forever for you to hand in your heart
But I keep on loving you and never depart
If perfection only existed in the virtual world
Would you love the real me?
Would you?
Do you know what 'Love' is?
I put freedom in your hands
For your desire to leave, I stand
Waiting for you at the end of the world
Whether or not you turn your head
Gutted, my sorrow stays in my heart
I always cherish your leaving heart
Maybe you won’t believe, even till the end
Yet I still keep on loving you without an end
I am Gloria
I am the 'Gloria' you created
It really hurts to be abandoned
However, I need to thank you
It’s you that gave me the chance to know about..
Love
..and it’s beautiful.
My only wish..
..is that you won't be giving up on yourself anymore
Chapter 12: One Minute
You
curl up your body
To protect that broken heart
With your back bathed in heavy sweats
Your
Your memories always rekindle
As if you are trapped in your awful dream
You wish to be awakened
Just as withering flowers that cannot stand gentle breeze
A slight wind will make you fall
You have never voiced out the burden borne
You want to pause the world for one minute
Let the beating heart stay still for one minute
You feel alone
Alone
So heavy-hearted
Come to my embrace
Let my heart break on your behalf
Let me enter your awful dream
To paint you a rainbow
Just pause the world for one minute
Let the beating heart stay still for one minute
You're not alone
Alone
I won't leave
If you want to cry, please do
Cry for a few more minutes
If you want to space out, please do
Space out for a few more minutes
You're not alone
I understand
Come to my embrace
Let my heart break on your behalf
Let me enter your awful dream
To paint your night with your stars returned
(The one you should love is across the street. 7th floor. Gloria.)
Chapter 13: The End of Night
I’d like you to share my secrets
I’d like you to touch my tears
I’d like to indulge with you even if we share silence
I’d like to give you all the time I have
If you let me
I want you to have my whole world
I want the stars to which you wish will stay with you till the end of this world
Just come with me
if this has become a raging world
Just let me stay with you in the search of our ark
To drift at the verge of freedom nights
I am the one that you've been looking for
Without you, my happiness is too weak to fill my heart
It’s you who makes happiness pure enough to warm my heart
Without you, the world is like a dessert
You are the stream in my dessert
If you let me
(If perfect only exist in the virtual world, would you still love the real me?
Do you believe he will love the real you?)
I want you to have my whole world
I want the stars to which you wish will stay with you till the end of this world
Just come with me
if this has become a raging world
Just let me stay with you in the search of our ark
To drift at the verge of freedom nights
Just come with me
The end of night
Is freedom
Just come with me
I'll take you away
The end of night
Is an eternity of freedom
I am the one that you've been looking for
The Way, The Truth, The Life
That you've been looking for
I am the one that you've been looking for
The Way, The Truth, The Life
If this has become a raging world
Just let me stay with you in the search of our ark
To drift at the verge of freedom nights
If this has become a raging world
Just let me stay with you in the search of our ark
To drift at the verge of freedom nights
An eternity of freedom
If this has become a raging world
Just let me stay with you in the search of our ark
To drift at the verge of freedom nights
An eternity of freedom
Chapter 14: The Sky
When I curiously play with black and white keys
When I hide in the room and perform with glee
Your smiling eyes seem to foretell
The vision of today
When I hear my favourite albums day and night
When I scribble chords over all pages of my books
You never quench my childish flame
You never blame my waste of time
It’s your unconditional love that makes me today
It’s you who show my path
The sky’s the limit
My future is boundless
Breaking the cocoon, I fly toward a brighter tomorrow
If the path ahead is a long way to go, just look back to my past
The one in the mirror has led the way for the past version of me
How far we’ve been through
So many occasions I have lost control
So many words from others that are stone cold
So many sleepless nights
Did you also feel that you are on the brink of collapse?
On this long and winding road
When I lonely await the returning spring
When I hold my tears to myself
One would blame when everything goes against one’s wish
Going through or backing down from such time, it's just in one thought
But you unconditionally bear all of these
It’s you who show me the way
The sky’s the limit
My future is boundless
Breaking the cocoon, I fly toward a brighter tomorrow
If the path ahead is a long way to go, just look back to my past
The one in the mirror has led the way for the past version of me
How far we’ve been through
(If perfection only exists in the virtual world)
How far we've been through
(Would you love the real me?)
We’ve been through a long way
(Do you believe he would love the real you?)
Looking back
How far I’ve come
Oh my world
I could not see its boundary
The sky’s the limit
My future is boundless
Breaking the cocoon, I fly toward a brighter tomorrow
If the path ahead is a long way to go, just look back to my past
(are you free tomorrow?)
The one in the mirror has led the way for the past version of me
How far we’ve been through
So many occasions I have lost control
So many words from others that are stone cold
So many sleepless nights
Did you also feel that you are on the brink of collapse
On this long and winding road
When I lonely await the returning spring
When I hold my tears to myself
When everything goes against your wish
Look at the blue sky
There’s no limit
All songs written by G.E.M.
All Glory to God